<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on /zxc/</title>
    <link>https://zxcnxc.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on /zxc/</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022, All.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zxcnxc.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Writeup LKSN ITNSA NTB 2021 - Packet Tracer Troubleshoot</title>
      <link>https://zxcnxc.github.io/writeup-lksn-itnsa-ntb-2021-packet-tracer-troubleshoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zxcnxc.github.io/writeup-lksn-itnsa-ntb-2021-packet-tracer-troubleshoot/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Introduction Troubleshooting 1 (Point: 25) Troubleshooting 2 (Point: 25) Troubleshooting 3 (Point: 25) Troubleshooting 4 (Point: 25) Summary Introduction Hello, everyone. Today&amp;rsquo;s post is based on the second of three questions titled &amp;ldquo;Packet Tracer Troubleshooting&amp;rdquo; that will be part of the NTB LKSN competition from ITNSA in 2021.
Unlike the previous question, this time, we are asked to troubleshoot the configuration of network devices with a predetermined network topology using Cisco Packet Tracer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writeup LKSN ITNSA NTB 2021 - Network Actual &amp; Future Network</title>
      <link>https://zxcnxc.github.io/writeup-lksn-itnsa-ntb-2021-network-actual-future-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zxcnxc.github.io/writeup-lksn-itnsa-ntb-2021-network-actual-future-network/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Introduction Task 1: HQ MATARAM Server Configuration Task 2: HQ MATARAM Router Configuration Task 3: SW_HQ_L1 Switch Configuration at HQ MATARAM Task 4: SW_HQ_L2 Switch Configuration at HQ MATARAM Task 5: Admin2 PC Configuration and Verification at HQ MATARAM Task 6: WLC Configuration at HQ MATARAM Task 7: LWAP Configuration at HQ MATARAM Task 8: End Device Configuration and Verification on HRD and MARKETING VLANs at HQ MATARAM Task 9: BRANCH SUMBAWA Server Configuration Task 10: BRANCH SUMBAWA Router Configuration Task 11: SW_BRANCH Switch Configuration at BRANCH SUMBAWA Task 12: DHCP Client Configuration and Internet Connection Verification on VLAN 2 SALES PC at BRANCH SUMBAWA Task 13: WRT_BRANCH Wireless Router Configuration at BRANCH SUMBAWA Task 14: End Device Configuration and Verification at WLAN ENGINEER BRANCH SUMBAWA Task 15: VPN configuration on an HQ MATARAM router using GRE over IPSec and OSPF Task 16: VPN configuration on a BRANCH SUMBAWA router using GRE over IPSec and OSPF Task 17: Verification of VPN Connection from End Device at HQ MATARAM Task 18: Verification of VPN Connection from End Device at BRANCH SUMBAWA Task 19: RBAC Configuration at router HQ MATARAM Task 20: RBAC Configuration at router BRANCH SUMBAWA Complete Configuration Summary Introduction This writeup is based on the first of three questions titled &amp;ldquo;Actual Networks &amp;amp; Future Networks&amp;rdquo; that were part of the NTB LKSN competition from ITNSA in 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eNSP VS WSL 2</title>
      <link>https://zxcnxc.github.io/ensp-vs-wsl-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zxcnxc.github.io/ensp-vs-wsl-2/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents TLDR Issues Setup Troubleshoot Summary TLDR Conflicts between Hypervisor.
Issues To learn more about Huawei devices, I decided to use the Huawei Enterprise Network Simulator Platform eNSP to simulate an enterprise network. So I followed the tutorial from an internet blog, but when I tried to run the program, I received the error message &amp;ldquo;Failed to start device AR1 error code 40.&amp;rdquo; in eNSP. Failed to start device AR1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://zxcnxc.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zxcnxc.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&#39;m ZXCNXC / All I work as a Fiber Optic Technician a.k.a FOT, my job is to configure network devices for remote monitoring of SCADA services and power plant PLCs. I created this blog just for personal documentation about Security, Networking and other things I am interested in.
PSA: Don&amp;rsquo;t hate me if the first thing you see is an anime picture or incorrect grammar and bad formatting of the post, I&amp;rsquo;m still trying to learn to fix for those things and I&amp;rsquo;m a weeb.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
